Oshi Culture Special Project
This March will be the group's third
live at Saitama Super Arena
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku
Their high performance has earned them the support of many fans.
In fact, they have many fans in the idol world as well.
The idols who love Ebisu Chugaku will talk about their charms!
What's more
What's so cute about that, ladies and gentlemen
It's like the dainty beauty of a Japanese woman.
It's like there's a huge gap between the two, like, can you do this too?
The members of Ebichu also share what they think is attractive about their idols.
The title of the talk was "Yale Exchange Idols.
Yale Exchange Idol: The Amazing Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku You Know Because You're an Idol!
Yale Exchange Idol
Which idol will deliver the first ale?
The morning chimes have sounded!
I'm Sanae, the fruit zipper!
I'm Manaka Mana, aka Manafin!
Pleased to meet you!
Fruit Zipper Manaka Mana or Mana
A seven-member idol group belonging to Asobi System, Fruit Zipper
Last May, we had a successful solo live at Nippon Budokan
And in June of this year
I know!
The new kawaii idol with the greatest momentum now is preparing to hold its 3rd anniversary live at Saitama Super Arena.
Here is what Debychu thinks of Manakamana!
Rika Mayama is a big fan of Manakamana, and she's a sure bet!
Mind Yankee Cocona Sakuragi says she can't get enough of Manaka's big sister feeling!
Manaka has been a fan of Ebichu since she was in junior high school.
Now that she has become an idol herself, Manaka says that there are some points that she recommends as a professional as well.
My live has a great atmosphere.
If I were to put it another way, it's like we're fighting.
It's like he's fighting with himself, the members, and all the fans of the EBITCHU family.
I really like that kind of all-out fighting.
Mind Yankee's style is like a bitch.
I think Bitsch's performance is amazing in its divergent power.
Of course, I think it's based on technique.
But they also compete with each other in friendly rivalry, singing and dancing like no one's ever beaten them.
It's really great that they show us how they all give their best to what they can do in each live performance.
That's what I really like about their performances.
Let's talk to Manaka-san, who is overflowing with love for Ebichu.
Manaka-san, who is overflowing with love for Ebichu, told us about his favorite Ebitu song and which Ebichu member he can't help but follow with his eyes!
First of all, let's start with the song that Manaka Manaka is jealous of in Ebitu!
It was completely and totally an Ebituu song for Ebituu!
It's not a fruit zipper song.
It's a song about Ebitu for Ebitu.
It is
Ebichu's song for Ebichu
I heard that all the Fruit Zippers had covered this song at Manaka-san's birthday event.
I thought it was really amazing.
I knew that they could perform that song with such a powerful energy and choreography, and sing it perfectly.
I'm really impressed by the way she choreographed and sang the song perfectly
and singing perfectly, while also showing her charm in her lines and giving off a warm and friendly vibe.
I knew it!
I can't do it normally.
It's because of her that those songs are possible.
They were probably written for her.
And Mana or the charming members that Mana can't help but follow with her eyes...
like their mouths are open and open and open, like they're coming out of here.
I really admire them a lot.
I can't believe they're younger than me, and I don't want to think that.
Here are the members
Thank you for your hard work!
This is the one that stopped time. Eternal Earth.
I loved Hinanu Kashiwagi so much.
But now that she graduated, Emma is taking over.
Orange.
I was really listening to it.
She sings in a way that makes me feel good.
If I could sing like this, I would definitely go to karaoke every day.
Karaoke is a waste of time.
Every day, every day.
Karaoke.
If you're going to Tokyo Dome or something, I'd rather you do a free concert every day and get a lot of people there.
I wonder what he's talking about.
I'm saying I want you to make it resonate.
Emma Sakurai, who received such a shout-out from the idols, said
I'm also usually impressed with that fruit zipper!
I've been listening to her songs on TikTok, and I've been getting a lot of buzz.
I've heard that Manaka Mana...
I was so surprised and happy to hear that Yamachan's song was listened to.
I'm so surprised and happy, I'm feeling so many emotions right now.
Here's Emma Sakurai's idol message to Manaka Mana
I have an image of sparkling cuteness.
The costumes are cute, and there's a song called "New Cute" where each one of us says something like, "This is really cute,
It's too cute, everyone.
The way they say it is so cute.
It's a song about love for the fans, and the way everyone says it, one by one, is so cute,
If it's the same as the legend as I think,
I thought, "Wow, that's great.
Next, which idol would give a shout out to Ebichu?
The morning chimes have sounded.
It's Ruru Danbara from Juice Juice!
Ruru Danbara of Juice Juice
Juice Juice belongs to Hello Project.
Juice Juice is a talented idol group that has attracted many fans with their solid performance ability.
Last June, they successfully held a one-man live concert at the Nippon Budokan.
Ruru Dambara became the fourth leader of the group.
Here is what Ebinaka thinks of Riru Danbara
Riko Nakayama was shocked by Mr. Danbara's singing voice when she heard it for the first time.
She begged to hear him sing live.
Many of the members are studying by watching JuiceJuice's live videos.
Ebinaka is also impressed by Ms. Danbara's overwhelming performance ability.
As a fellow idol, what is Ebichu's favorite thing about JuiceJuice's music?
Delicious!
Her facial expression and heat.
Heat rides on his voice and it's easy to ride on it.
I have the impression that there are many members who sing with their faces.
Of course, we also use all of our facial expressions.
Not only with our voices, but also with our movements, angles, and facial expressions.
We also use our facial expressions to convey the message.
Ebinaka-san, you bring the power of the song to life in your voice.
You add the power of the song to your voice and facial expressions.
Ebinaka-san adds the power of the song with his voice and facial expressions and conveys it to the audience.
The energy of the song is directly conveyed through the members' voices.
Ms. Dambara says she is fascinated by the rich expressions on the faces of the singers, so much so that she feels as if they are singing with their faces.
There are a lot of powerful and energetic songs in the band.
It's like a fresh and cute youth song.
That glittering, splashing feeling is something you don't see in Juice's live performances.
I thought it was Ebinaka's personality.
I asked Ruru Danbara to tell me what song she envies Ebichu's favorite song.
When this song is played at the end of the live, everyone gets excited and we get excited too.
The way the members looked at each other and sang the song while harmonizing with each other was really cool.
Here is the song
I'll sing until I reach you
We have something we want to deliver to all over the world
Hot!
Hot! It's so hot, I don't know what to call it.
Refreshingly hot
I don't know if I can do it with juice.
I'd like to try it.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Next, a member I couldn't help but follow with my eyes.
I heard that there is a singing scene that makes you long for it.
I've never heard it live.
I've never heard it live, but I'd love to hear the part where she sings "Straight Away"...
I'd like to hear it live someday.
It's so cool!
So cool!
What Danbaralulu wishes to hear live is
Straight solo part
It sounds difficult, doesn't it?
I'd rather listen to it than have it covered by us.
I'd like to hear you sing it.
I've seen the live version before.
the last part of the last chorus.
It's a song by Juice Juice.
Ayaka and I
Ayaka and I were talking about doing a fake exchange
and we were talking about doing a fake dialogue.
with a euphoric feeling.
Good night.
We were faking each other in the space.
It wasn't like a great battle.
It wasn't like a great battle, but we were raising each other's spirits.
I thought it would be great if we could fake it.
It was a lot of fun!
I'm very curious about how Yasumoto-san always sings.
I'm very curious about how Yasumoto-san always sings, and I'd like to talk to him about it.
What about Ayaka Yasumoto, the recipient of the idol yell?
Lulu has been leading JuiceJuice since the group was formed, and she's a very encouraging member.
I think she's a very encouraging member of JuiceJuice.
As a JuiceJuice fan, I have her as my target.
I'm so happy that Lulu-chan praised my Ebituyu.
I'm a little bit embarrassed and happy.
I'm embarrassed and happy, and I'm so thankful.
Here's an idol yell from Ayaka Yasumoto to Lulu Danbara. Lulu's singing is really good because of the way she accentuates her voice.
I think it's so cool and musical, and only Lulu can do it.
The way she sings, the way she looks at the audience, the way she looks at the audience.
The way you look at the audience while singing, the way you look at them, the way you look straight at them when you make a decision...
I think it's really cool how you capture and incorporate these elements into the music and the sound.
I'm always glued to the stage and can't take my eyes off of them.
I think all idols are jealous of this song.
"I feel like I can live on my own..." That's a compliment.
I'm really jealous of that song, it's so good!
Juice Juice has a soulful and passionate voice, but she doesn't show it in her facial expressions or her posture.
It's like the soul of a strong woman hidden inside, and she dares to hide her soul behind her back.
I really like and admire the dainty beauty of Japanese women.
I really like and admire it.
I want to imitate her, but I think it's a charm I can't quite achieve.
After the exchange of idol yell, let's continue.
Yes, I'm Miki Ito from SKE48 Team K2. I'm Miki Ito from SKE48 Team K2, and I'm also a member of the Ebitu family.
SKE48 Miki Ito
Miki Ito is a member of SKE48, an idol group based in Sakae, Nagoya.
In October, she was ranked first in the Sasuke Idol Preliminary Round and competed in the terrestrial finals.
She is an idol who is also very active in the field of sports.
Here is what Ebitu thinks of Miki Ito.
Many members are surprised at her athletic ability, and some say they are glad that she is an Ebichu guess.
Ms. Ito says that she goes to Ebitu's live performances in private.
As a fellow idol, he has this point of guess.
I have the image of Nebichu-san using a lot of hand microphones.
But Nebichu's full-body movement makes the hand mic look like a headset.
The performance is so big that it looks like a headset.
I really respect him because he is so athletic.
Before I became an idol, I was just looking at them as fun and cute.
I used to watch them just for fun or to see how cute they were.
But nowadays, I respect them so much for being able to sing
I have a lot of respect for their ability to sing and dance in a way that I never had before.
He pointed out that ske 48 has a reputation for its dancing. He said that Ebichu's performance was so amazing that he didn't even feel that he was holding a handheld microphone.
And there is another reason why Mr. Ito is crazy about Ebichu... The oshimen is Yuna Nakamura.
I was really attracted to her singing voice during the live performance.
I was really attracted to her singing voice.
Here is Yuna Nakamura's singing voice that captivated Miki Ito
It comes straight from the heart.
But it really sticks.
I don't know what it is, the transparency and straightness.
It really sticks with you.
I really love it!
As both a fan and a professional
Mr. Ito, who respects Debychu as both a fan and a professional
I hope you enjoy the music that I envy.
I'm looking forward to it!
Every time, the tension of the members at that time
and the feelings of the members at that time
I think the way they sing changes a lot depending on how they are feeling at the time.
Mr. Ito's favorite song is "Yale", a standard song at Ebitu live.
The Yell you hear on your cell phone is totally different from the Yell you hear at the live performance.
The yell sung by Ebichu really stuck with me.
I thought that the influence that Ebitu-san had on me was amazing.
I want to be someone who can encourage my fans with my songs.
I want to be the one who can give energy to the fans with such songs.
I heard that you love to see Ebitu perform live.
I heard that you love EBITCHU's performance.
I heard that there are members of the group who can't help but look at him as a professional idol as well, and they rave that they can watch him for the rest of their lives
He said he could watch them for the rest of his life.
Here is the performance
She said she loves Ebitu's performance.
I really like your style, Cocona.
I think she has a great style.
The angles of her body
I can't help but admire her style and the angles of her body.
Cocona received a shout out from Miki Ito.
Ebitu Sakuragi Cocona?
Is it over?
It's over!
I'm so happy, I feel so good!
I'm so happy that I'd be happy even if we had another 15 minutes or so.
Just a little bit more.
I've been dancing since I was 6 years old, and it's my favorite genre.
I've been dancing since I was 6 years old, and I love it.
I was so happy to hear you say you like it.
Here, Cocona Sakuragi gives an idol shout-out to Miki Ito.
In my opinion, SKE is really cute and pure and beautiful, like dancing angels.
There are many SKE members, aren't there?
That's the image I had of SKE.
But the songs "Absolute Inspiration" and "Confessions of a Heartbeat" have such a strong dance performance.
It's like...
What do you call it? Of course I can dance, but I felt like I was in a really beautiful world, so I wondered if I could do it too.
There were so many of them, and yet each one of them danced so well.
Seeing how well SKE's dancers danced together, I thought, "Oh my God, we really need to have all 9 dancers dancing together.
I was reminded of that again.
Miki Ito is such a pretty, calm, chatty and talkative person.
I was surprised at the gap between her being such a cute, calm, chatty talker and being an athletic person.
I was betrayed in a good way.
Thank you Manaka Mana, Ruru Danbara, and Miki Ito for your yells full of love!